i-funbox.com 2016-10-19

# iFunbox | the File and App Management Tool for iPhone, iPad & iPod Touch.

**Privacy Statement**   
iFunBox is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This Privacy Statement only covers the site iFunBox. 

**Aggregated Information**   
Aggregated information, such as which page users access or visit, and information volunteered by users is collected through various methods. For example, iFunBox collects IP addresses; an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers (the computers that "serve up" Web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address; when you request a page from iFunBox, our servers log your IP address. iFunBox only uses IP addresses for the purposes of Web traffic analysis and trends. 

**Use of Cookies**   
iFunBox uses cookies for this site. A cookie is a small data file that most major websites write to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow iFunBox to measure activity on the site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences. 

**Children and Privacy**   
iFunBox encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children. 

**Individuals under 13**   
No information should be submitted on iFunBox by users under the age of 13 years without consent of their parent or guardian. iFunBox does not provide any personally-identifying information for users under the age of 13, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever unless disclosed during collection. 

**Links to Other Sites**   
iFunBox contains links to sites other than iFunBox; those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as iFunBox. 

**Effect of Privacy Policy**   
This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party. iFunBox reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time and users will be notified of any changes made. 

**USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR CONSENT TO THIS ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE.**
